Welcome back to my series where I
recreate Dairy Queen Blizzard flavors,
but lower in calories and higher in
protein. This is the cotton candy
blizzard. Let me show you how to make
it. You're going to need some kind of
high protein milk, sweetener, salt,
zantham gum, and then the key ingredient
is cotton candy extract. I use this one
from Lauran. It's great. Just don't use
too much because it is very, very
potent. And yes, I did add some red
cordi off camera. I didn't want to
offend anything. You literally don't
have to add it. But after your pine is
completely frozen, take it out, run it
under hot water for about a minute, and
then throw it in your creamy on the
light ice cream setting. I only needed
one spin. You might have to do two or
three. It really depends on your
machine, how frozen it is, and the exact
ingredients you use. So, once it's
looking good and creamy, we can take
some kind of pink and purple candy or
sprinkle, whatever you got. I found
these little candy ones at Marshalls.
Throw them on top and mix them in by
hand.